You two look like a couple.
Is there something going on?
Oh! I'm sorry.
The path is pretty wide.
Did you do that on purpose?
Why did you follow me here?
Did I? I was jogging after practice.
You should apply to be an intern
for the soccer club.
The team really needs extra hands.
The two of us
are dating.
Hey.
Why do I have to see you everywhere?
I've been feeling a bit uneasy lately, Jinna.
[Go to hell]
Anyway, be careful for now, Anda.
This clearly was sent with bad intentions.
Podduang.
Wake up. You're home.
Yes, baby.
He's really out cold, huh?
Your stir-fried veggies are here, baby.
Not even gonna wait?
What?!
Are you gonna follow me everywhere or what?!
Uh...
I'm sorry, dear.
I'm not...
- Uh... I'm leaving the elevator.
- Oh... I'm so sorry.
- Right.
- I'm sorry, ma'am.
Right, right. I'm sorry.
Hey, Podduang.
I saw a young man drop you off last night.
So dope.
Awesome stuff.
Are you the one who called
a ride to the university?
Uh... Yes.
Hop on, kiddo.
[The characters, organizations,
and events depicted in this series
are entirely fictional
and intended solely for entertainment.
The series does not endorse
any behavior depicted.
Viewer discretion is advised]
♫I once sought an answer♫
♫To what we were together♫
♫Love, as I used to see it,♫
♫Couldn't flourish without clarity♫
♫It took a long time♫
♫To realize what is important♫
♫There are no rules♫
♫To love that we wish to bloom♫
♫Simply recognizing♫
♫What your heart is desiring♫
♫Is enough♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫Nothing else matters to me, it's true♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫No matter how tough the world may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫
[Oops! Mysterious Sounds]
You did so well, you know?
But...
Don't watch the next scene, Kum.
Why not?
It makes me flustered.
Let's watch it, then,
hm?
No, don't.
Totally killed it.
I told you not to watch it.
You're so different from
your character in the series.
What?
Are you jealous?
Nothing.
I know
how to make it up to you.
See?
You're teasing this old dog's heart again.
Huh?
What do you mean?
A short ad break first.
Huh?
Give me a second.
Ta-da...
For you.
What is it?
Open it.
[Anda]
Whoa...
Do you like it?
This is lovely.
Notice the number right here.
Wow...
This is really sweet.
You're my first Andaman.
Mm...
With this,
how should I reward my good boy?
What's the reward?
Just keep watching the series.
We're about to reach the climax.
Are we now?
The climax in...
We're about to reach the climax, right?
The tension's rising.
What?
That's not what I mean, Kum.
Hm?
Stop it.
Well...
Thank you very much, everyone,
for making it here today.
I'm really excited
that we'll get to watch the ending together.
How do you feel about the series
still going so strong right now,
while also trending at number one
in both Thailand and neighboring countries?
I'm so delighted.
And...
Thank you for all the support
you've given us both.
Is it true that you and Anda
are about to release merchandise
for fans to collect?
Can you give us a little sneak peek
at what it will look like?
I believe our fans will love it.
Here's a hint:
you can combine two parts into one.
Oh, how sweet!
Oh, one more thing.
There are only 100 of these, everyone.
If you want to get your hands on one,
tonight at 7 P.M.,
click the link on the series'
social media pages.
After three series together,
when will you two finally make it official?
When should we announce it?
What is this?
Oh...
Anda?
You don't need to go full incognito like this.
I want to stay by your side.
I miss you, Kum.
Don't give me that smile.
Make sure to get some rest, okay?
I've got you right here,
my good source of rest.
Come and let me recharge.
What are you doing?
Nobody will see us.
I hopped on Chai's van
and had him drive around
the parking lot so many times.
Then, I got changed and came here.
Rest assured.
Seems like a total hassle, doesn't it?
Mm...
It does...
That's why I deserve a reward.
What are you doing?
Come on.
The windows are tinted.
No one can see us.
Kum.
I want to go public.
Is that a good idea, Anda?
This might affect your career.
I'm just done dating you in secret.
I won't have to go full incognito
like what I've been doing either.
You're gaining popularity, Anda.
You're rising to fame.
I think
we don't have to go public.
I'm fine as it is.
But isn't it uncomfortable?
Not being able to be ourselves?
Your family isn't okay with this, are they?
Your father hasn't been in touch with you
since you started working on a series,
Hey...
Anda.
I'll leave this to you.
I myself
can handle it just fine.
You can take your time.
For me,
simply being with you
is already enough to make me happy.
See?
You're always like this.
How can I not love this old dog?
Kiss me.
Let's hit the road now.
Podduang.
You sure your internet connection is fast enough?
It's slowing down because of Dunk.
He's glued to his soccer game.
Dunk, turn it off already.
Hey, what the hell?
The match is just as important.
Right now,
there's nothing as important
as the 100 figurines.
You're so right.
30 seconds left.
If I reset the router right now,
would you be mad at me?
- Shut up!
- Shut it!
Why not make more if you knew it'd sell?
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
[Surfer boy]
Six...
- Five...
- Four...
- Three.
Two...
[Buy It Now]
One...
[Sorry, the website is temporarily unavailable]
Damn it...
It always happens to me.
What?
What's happening?
What the fuck happened?
Why are you all quiet?
I'm nervous, okay?
[SOLD OUT]
Ah!
It's fucking over,
my limited edition collection!
I'm so upset, Bumm.
No...
Don't touch me!
Oh...
She's pissed.
Better leave her be.
Who the hell is that?
I'm so sad...
Who is it?
What's wrong?
You're acting like it's Jinna.
Did you forget about your order?
You didn't answer my calls.
Sorry.
Jinna!
You're such a hard worker,
delivering food even on your day off.
How many jobs do you have?
He reminds me of Chief Hong from
'Hometown Cha-Cha-Cha.'
I never knew people like this existed.
Come and hang out with us.
I have other work to do.
See you at the soccer club.
Dunk,
why are you inviting him in?
This is my place!
Sorry, I...
I was being too friendly...
Hey, come on now.
Let's have dinner.
Yours first.
What is it?
I don't know.
[Anda Confirms His Relationship
with Non-Celebrity Partner!]
Hello, Podduang?
Hello, Bumm.
Have you seen the news?
I have. I've been waiting for you.
What made you decide to make such a bold move?
I believe the series I've worked on
taught me that "love has no bounds."
And I...
I want everyone to know that
I stand by the message
that this is who I really am.
I wanted to come on this show first
to remind everyone that
we all deserve to love and be loved
in our own way.
Are you worried your popularity might fade
after going public?
This has been something
I've thought about for a long time.
But I've thought it through.
I think it's worth it.
I also believe the fans of the series
and the Andaman fandom
will understand.
Have you consulted anyone
before making the announcement?
I consulted my partner.
Is your partner a celebrity
or a non-celebrity?
Non-celebrity.
A pilot.
A pilot?
What did your family say about this?
I hope they'll understand me.
[#AndaIsNotManly]
[The sausage-fest will rule the world.
#AndaIsNotManly]
[This is rude.
It takes a lot for someone to come out.
Why the bullying in this day and age?]
[Mess with my baby and
you mess with me, walking red flags]
[Anda's being a twink new to you?
Heard he got ass-fucked by a soccer player]
[Your words reflect your upbringing]
[#AndaIsNotManly Never cared about this partner.
Is the trend because of James?]
[Anda did nothing wrong.
People want to stir the pot now that he's famous]
[I'm rooting for you, Anda.
I actually don't want to use #AndaIsNotManly at all.
#AndaAndHisSmile]
[Love you, Anda. We're so proud of you
for being yourself #AndaAndHisSmile]
This isn't good.
So many people reposted my tweets.
All I see are homophobes.
A lot of the fans
are showing him support, though.
There's nothing we can do.
We don't even know how Anda is holding up.
Yeah.
So...
How are you and Dunk doing?
Well...
It's going alright.
We've gotten used to each other.
It feels like we're more like
friends than anything.
It's hard to explain.
Mm.
Podduang.
Honestly,
I'm a little uncomfortable
about dating Dunk.
I'm...
I'm so afraid.
From our first year until now,
we know what we're like.
You know what I'm like.
My love life always comes crashing down.
I think this one's on me, really.
It probably won't be the case with Dunk.
Don't know.
Don't want to think about it.
You've been his crush since freshman year.
And what about you?
When did he become your crush?
I care about you, Podduang.
I care so much about our group.
Me too.
But as for your relationship,
I'm actually okay with it.
Don't worry, Bumm.
Your phone's out of juice.
Now, you can look up the chords.
Hey, it's okay.
I'm leaving soon.
Come on, just take it.
If you rent a portable charger here,
you can return it at any station.
Okay.
Oh?
What's wrong, Podduang?
You don't look okay, Podduang.
It...It's not about that, Bumm.
What?
Why am I out of the loop?
It's within the Andaman fandom.
It's about my internship hours
with the core team.
I still don't know which team I should join.
I told you to join the soccer team with me.
Why complicate things?
No way!
I hate Jinna.
I'll join the basketball team.
It's already full.
Where have you been?
And the volleyball team?
Also full!
The rugby team doesn't sound so bad.
Full!
The swimming team?
Also...
Full!
What now?
Do I have to be with the chess team?
That team's not full,
but it's not on the list.
Though I think...
the soccer team isn't a bad idea.
Jinna isn't that bad of a guy.
Dunk is on the team, too.
I always come to watch him play.
You won't be lonely.
Do you guys notice something?
Whenever we have a problem,
we always sit on this damn bench.
Should I just break it?
Nonsense.
[DOT: DREAMS OF TOMORROW]
You almost bumped into me
and ran off again.
Is Coach Kong here?
You came.
At this rate...
who's actually following who, I wonder?
I joined the club
because my friend is on the team.
I didn't want to see you.
On top of that,
it's almost time to submit the document.
I don't want to intern next semester.
I already knew that.
You explained like something was up.
Why getting on my nerves so much?
I'm getting on your nerves?
You're the only one
who doesn't like me.
Be honest.
Are you mad at me or what?
Or am I making you blush?!
Alright, everyone.
This is an intern from
the Faculty of Sports and Health Science,
who will assist you this semester.
Give him a round of applause
to welcome him.
Take care of him, everyone.
♫I once sought an answer♫
♫To what we were together♫
♫Love, as I used to see it,♫
♫Couldn't flourish without clarity♫
♫It took a long time♫
Hey, pick up the pace. Keep it up.
Keep the triangle going.
There, there. That's up, back,
and then through.
♫There are no rules♫
♫To love that we wish to bloom♫
♫Simply recognizing♫
♫What your heart is desiring♫
♫Is enough♫
Podduang.
What is it, Bumm?
You seem pretty quiet.
I'm sorry if I'm misunderstanding you,
but I think you're lying to me.
I'm fine, really.
I feel like...
I'm hurting your feelings.
I'm willing to go back
to just being friends with Dunk, Podduang.
If there's something you're not okay with,
you can just tell me.
I'm serious.
Bumm,
calm down and...
listen to me.
I just...
used to have a crush on Dunk.
But I'm okay now.
Do you understand where I'm coming from?
I...
I've been disappointed
by this kind of thing so many times.
And I don't want to disappoint
or have problems with my two best friends.
I've got someone I like now.
Huh?
I'm sorry?
Well...
We've started seeing each other.
Who is it?
It's Jinna.
Huh?
Jinna?
You mean that Jinna?
Which Jinna?
It's that Jinna, alright?
The Jinna.
Damn it...
What did I just tell her?
Please, calm down, honey.
Anda.
Why did you come home so early?
I want to see you, Mom.
Gosh.
You know what your dad is like lately.
And what about you?
Are you okay
with...
what I said in the announcement?
You already know how I feel.
I still love you like I always have,
but you need to find some time
to talk to your dad.
But I think...
it's best to wait until he's a bit calmer.
Am I so wrong
that this is who I am?
And...
Does your brother know about this?
He doesn't.
I hope...
Itti will understand me.
Everyone's left.
Need something?
Uh...
Jinna, I...
You like me?
Not that.
I don't like you,
and there's no way I would.
Why did you say that, then?
I just...
I just want to
make my best friend feel better.
By lying that you're seeing me?
For what?
Fine. I'm sorry, then.
I didn't mean to tell her that.
I just...
didn't want to hurt my friend's feelings.
That means...
You and Bumm like the same person?
Dunk, is it?
Since I already used
your name as an excuse,
can you hit on me?
What did you just say?
I know you heard me.
Can you pretend you're hitting on me?
And...
Why would I do that?
You asked me what I was mad at you about.
And?
If you pretend to hit on me, I'll...
I'll let it go and stop being mad at you.
Please?
Just for a month.
I'm only asking for a month.
A month?
Okay.
And that means...?
I'll
hit
on
you.
Do you two realize
you've been acting really strange?
Seriously,
when did you and Jinna start talking?
Well...
Why?
Worried about your friend?
I don't get it.
I'm confused.
Tell me I'm not dreaming.
Ow...
What dreaming?
Fine!
I believe now.
You shook my head so hard
my brain's all upside down.
Well, just in case you're still dreaming.
From now on, I hope you don't mind
if I hit on your buddy, okay?
Sure.
No problem.
He's yours.
Dig in.
So bland.
Yeah, so is my drink.
What? Are you kidding me?
Let me have a sip.
Hey...
You want my drink, don't you?
Not a chance.
I want to drink some Thai tea, too. Let's share.
Podduang!
I got you a bag of cocoa.
My heart's about to stop.
It's okay.
I'll call for a rescue team.
[Following]
I think Podduang made the first move.
You're wrong.
From the looks of it,
it was definitely Jinna.
Do you know what
physiological arousal fucking means?
There's this thing about
people who hate each other,
where being in the same room
makes their hearts start racing.
They'll break into a sweat,
turn red,
and get an adrenaline rush.
Podduang is an intern at the soccer club.
He's bound to feel something.
Gosh.
You've got it all wrong, Tod.
When it comes to this,
it's either the right person or the wrong one.
Podduang hates Jinna's guts.
And you should stop it right now,
with those silly theories you read in books.
Jinna.
Who made the first move?
What the hell?
I don't buy it.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Jinna really is hitting on me.
Are you really okay with this?
You hate his guts.
Well, I...
I want to open up to him.
Didn't you two tell me...
he's not a bad guy?
Jeez...
And now you're acting all confused.
Yeah.
Believe what he said, Dunk.
Fine.
I'm still a bit shocked.
I'm sorry.
Nonsense.
And...
Where are you two at now?
It's not official yet.
We're just...
seeing where things go.
Sheesh...
Is my friend about to get into a relationship?
If that's the case,
the rivalry between the two faculties is over.
Now they're two loving faculties.
Stop that now.
When are you going to return my earphones?
What? Come on...
You got so flustered
you had to change the subject?
You're getting carried away.
Ow...
What's wrong, babe?
You called me "babe"?
Yuck.
Don't call me that again.
I don't like it.
Just kidding.
Uh, yeah, I forgot them at my place.
I'll return them later.
You lost them, didn't you?
Lost? That's ridiculous.
I'll return them soon, Podduang.
Always.
Right.
Have you seen Anda at all?
I haven't seen him
since the controversy.
But things have gotten a lot better.
People understand him a lot better now.
Yeah.
The world has changed a lot.
Even I understand him.
Mm.
Glad things are turning around for him.
I don't want him to stress out.
[I don't know where Anda has gone,
but we, the Andaman fandom,
are always right here. #AndaAndHisSmile]
[I love #AndaAndHisSmile so much.
If you came across this hashtag,
I hope you can take our love and support with you]
[The Andaman fandom,
please show him our support. #AndaAndHisSmile]
[Is the #AndaAndHisSmile
necessary for a gay person dating someone?]
[None of your business.
If you can't think of anything positive,
then shut up. #AndaAndHisSmile]
[People leaving rude comments
are just jealous.
Did no one ever love them? #AndaAndHisSmile]
[Bumm: I'm so happy our hashtag
has reached the number one trend]
[Podduang: Muah, muah]
On this episode of 'Woody Talk,' we're with Anda,
a renowned actor who's at
the center of attention right now.
Are you a fan of Anda?
Oh, yes.
Same, actually.
I also love the Andaman fandom.
Can I watch this with you?
No problem.
He's adorable, isn't he?
He really is.
How long have you been his fan?
Mm...
About two or three years. What about you?
Oh, same, actually.
About that long for me too.
But it's a shame
he's been getting so much hate lately.
These toxic netizens who just keep hating
are out of their minds, aren't they?
Yeah.
I feel so bad for him.
Oh?
You didn't press the button?
I got distracted.
- Oh, Anda is just too adorable.
- I'm sorry.
Perfect timing.
He's cute, isn't he?
Aww,
and when Anda acted with James...
Look, this beach scene is just...
- so great.
- Oh.
I saved this one too.
- Oh, really?
- It's such a beautiful scene.
Oh.
This is my room.
Huh?
We're basically neighbors.
Hey!
Are you kidding me?
But
we've never seen each other before, have we?
You're right.
What a coincidence.
Right. My name is Amp.
If you have any problems, feel free to
knock on my door.
My name is
Podduang.
You can also simply call me "Pod."
Okay.
See you.
Right. Bye-bye.
[JINNA]
[Hello]
It's hard to live as a celebrity, isn't it?
Even admitting who you like feels like a crime.
Mm.
Are you okay?
I heard you had it rough.
I was too scared to message you.
I was afraid you weren't ready to open up.
It was brutal, actually.
Why is it so hard to be myself?
Because our lives...
don't simply depend on ourselves, Anda.
You're right.
Ever since I made the announcement,
I feel like I'm completely lost.
So lost that sometimes I ask myself
if I've...
actually slipped up.
My company even gave me a warning.
Even worse,
my manager
told me that...
all the upcoming series
we were supposed to shoot
have been put on hold.
On top of that, someone sent me
that freaky doll, too.
Do that many people
really hate me, Jinna?
I'm so tired, Jinna.
I'm so tired.
Then come back to us.
Having known you for three years,
you're certainly loved by so many more.
I don't mean to get all emotional,
but like...
Since I started working as an actor,
I've gotten to know so many people,
but you three are the only ones
I can really talk to about everything.
Right.
Art, Tod, and I are always here.
Everything is just piling up on me...
and I have no idea where to even start.
My family wasn't okay with
my announcement either.
They haven't been okay with me
being an actor from day one.
Anda.
Someday, your family will
appreciate your effort.
One step at a time, okay?
Anda.
You're looking really run-down these days.
Don't forget to make some time to rest.
I'm worried about you.
So are Tod and Art.
Thank you.
It's okay, it's okay.
- What class do you have today, Jinna?
- Hey...
- Professor Bankpan is so strict.
- I'm done.
I don't want to study with him at all.
He really is.
Oh.
That's Podduang and Bumm.
I'll be right back.
I wonder who he's seeing.
Showing his true colors already.
Hello.
Hello to whom?
Me?
Or that girl?
What?
Jealous?
I'm here too, you know?
What's with all the sweet talk?
You didn't reply to my DMs.
I'd already fallen asleep.
Mm.
This is...
Risa, a scholarship student in Accounting.
We go back to freshman year.
Hello, Podduang.
Hello, Bumm.
I'm Risa.
Nice to meet you all.
Right.
I have a class to attend.
We're running late, too.
Let's go.
Hey...
Hold on.
- Bye-bye.
Hurry.
We're late.
They all seem very friendly.
Well...
Isn't that nice?
Who would want to be like you anyway?
[Faculty of Engineering]
Should we have steak at our usual place?
Anda is here after all.
Let's.
I'm in.
But I think...
Anda probably wants to go to
our favorite shabu-shabu place, doesn't he?
That's a good idea.
Art.
- What?
- Do you really have to oppose everything I say?
Come on...
It's called "presenting an option."
I'm fine with anything, actually.
But...
Shabu-shabu might be a better choice?
Steak is better.
Shabu-shabu.
Steak.
- I've got it.
- Shabu-shabu.
Shabu-shabu?
A pad kaphrao place by the university.
- Oh...
- Oh, come on...
Seriously?
Come on, let's go.
Anda.
We need to talk.
Hey, wait a minute.
Who are you?
We need to talk,
just the two of us.
Just talk about it here.
Why do you need to talk to him alone?
Just tell us.
Can you stay the fuck away?!
Art, calm down.
Let me talk.
Calm down, calm down.
Listen to him. Let's not make any sudden moves.
Wait and see.
Why are you so fucking selfish, Anda?
Why did you have to ruin someone else's life too?
Do you know
the company...
didn't just put your series on hold?
This affects me, too.
We're the lead partners.
Why did you have to
ruin my life as well?!
James, I'm deeply sorry.
Sorry.
Sorry for fucking what,
huh?
Back then,
I liked you
because I really did.
When you rejected me,
I respected your decision,
but I never fucking mixed this shit with work!
I didn't do it because
I was uncomfortable with you.
I just didn't want to pretend
and keep lying to people.
That's all!
What about our partner projects?
You can't just be whoever the fuck
you want to be.
Aren't you being too selfish, Anda?
With this kind of stuff,
there are seniors
and businesses tied to it.
I just want you and me to make the most of it.
Once it's over, whoever you want to flirt with
or sleep with is up to you!
James, calm down!
Are you...
Are you that thirsty for a sleeping partner?!
Huh?!
I never knew you'd be like this.
And so fucking what, Anda?!
Hey!
Seems like you've got a problem.
Hey, you.
I hope you don't do something stupid
on our turf,
with our tools
and our friends around.
Leave now
if you don't want to make the headlines.
You...
All of you
better get used to fucking dealing with me.
Hey.
Hey...
Listen to me.
Hey!
Hands off!
Leave already.
I don't want to see you anymore.
No.
I'm here because I want to hear from you
that you hate me.
Yes.
Tell him, "I hate you!"
Please listen to me.
No!
Hey...
I hate you.
I hate you!
Are you satisfied now?!
I really am!
But I didn't order anything?
I've got you this.
I think you'll like it.
What is it?
Open it.
I want to see your reactions.
I only asked you to pretend to
flirt with me, you know?
You don't have to go this far...
Where did you get this?!
Hey,
Anda.
I need your help.
♫Caught off guard, I don't know what to do♫
♫I'm gonna tell you how much I love you♫
I'm sorry...
I didn't mean it.
It's okay.
Uh...
♫I've got feelings for you out of the blue♫
♫I suddenly fell for you♫
♫When has this become the truth?♫
I have to go now.
Hey.
- This is your room...
- Oh.
Bye-bye.
♫Missing you means I love you, yeah?♫
♫I'm thinking of you again♫
♫Even in my sleep♫
♫And even when I eat, and it's kinda dangerous♫
♫I've figured it out, it's love♫
♫Should I confess it?
Will I get heartbroken? I can't hold it♫
♫I brushed it off,
'cause I thought I was being lonely♫
♫But you came to me, without even a tease♫
♫You looked nothing fancy,
but you were so adorable♫
[Mentioned you in their story]
[So cute]
♫Caught off guard, I don't know what to do♫
♫I'm gonna tell you how much I love you♫
♫I've got feelings for you out of the blue♫
♫I suddenly fall for you♫
♫When has this become the truth?♫
♫Fallen for you without a clue♫
♫I love you through and through♫
♫Since Day 1,
have I really been having a crush on you?♫
Jinna.
I really like you.
What the hell?
That came out of nowhere.
You know how hot Jinna is, right?
I only want you to pretend to hit on me.
Don't get too attached.
I don't like pretending, though.
You've been practicing hard today,
so I got you some water.
- For me?
- Mm.
This award is for you all.
[Team Anda]
You're standing here arguing with me nonstop,
and you actually expect me
to be proud of your stupid award?
Will there be a day when my dad accepts me?
At the end of the day,
I feel like I can never truly be myself
as long as I'm still alive.
I just want to tell you that
if you're hurting,
just let it out.
Don't worry about how people will see you.
♫I once sought an answer♫
♫To what we were together♫
♫Love, as I used to see it,♫
♫Couldn't flourish without clarity♫
♫It took a long time♫
♫To realize what is important♫
♫There are no rules♫
♫To love that we wish to bloom♫
♫Simply recognizing♫
♫What your heart is desiring♫
♫Is enough♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫Nothing else matters to me, it's true♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫No matter how tough the world may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫
♫I rest my hands♫
♫Holding on to yours♫
♫You chased away♫
♫My uncertainty♫
♫No words were said,♫
♫But I hear you♫
♫Loud and clear♫
♫It’s meant to be♫
♫Simply recognizing♫
♫What your heart is desiring♫
♫Is enough♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫Nothing else matters to me, it's true♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫No matter how tough the world may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫No matter how tough the world may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫